ILGWU. Publications 5780 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Pittston Guide, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  v.9: no.2 (1982: Fall); Copy #2
- Pittston Guide, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  v.10: no.1 (1983: Spring)
- Pittston, PA, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  v.10: no.1 (1983: Spring); Copy #2
- Pittston, PA, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  v.10: no.2 (1983: Fall)
- Pittston, PA, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  v.10: no.2 (1983: Fall); Copy #2
- Pittston, PA, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  v.1: no.2 (1963: May)
- Pittston, Guide, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  v.2: no.1 (1964: Mar)
- Pittston, PA, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  v.2: no.1 (1964, Mar); Copy #2
- Pittston, PA, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  v.2: no.1 (1964: Mar); Copy #3
- Pittston, PA, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  v.1: no.4 (1964: Dec)
- Pittston, PA, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  v.1: no.4 (1964: Dec) Copy #2
- Pittston, PA, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  v.1: no.5 (1965: Dec)
- Pittston, PA, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  v.1: no.6 (1966: Dec)
- Pittston, PA, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  v.1: no.7 (1967: Dec)
- Pittston, PA, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  v.1: n.7 (1967: Dec); Copy #2
- Pittston, PA, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  v.1: no.7 (1967: Dec); Copy #3
- Pittston, PA, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  v.1: no.8 (1968: Dec)
- Pittston, PA, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  v.1: no.8 (1968: Dec); Copy #2
- Solidarity, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 49)
  v.4: no.1 (1977: Oct)
- Retirement Dinner: Clem Lyons, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 50)
- Retirement Dinner: Clem Lyons, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 50)
- Retirement Dinner: Leon Saslaw, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 50)
- Pauline Newman (1893-1986) (Box 71, Folder 50)
- The Sol C. Chaikin Testimonial Dinner, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 50)
  Event Program
- Retirement Dinner: Jack Sobel, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 50)
- A Dinner Retirement of Jane Paluscio, District Manager, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 50)
- Newsletter for Staff, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  v.4: no.1 (1984: Winter)
- ILGWU Guide on Agreement Provisions, Standards and Enforcement (Box 72, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Guide on Agreement Provisions, Standards and Enforcement (Box 72, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Guide on Agreement Provisions, Standards and Enforcement (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Guide for Medical Aides (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Guide for Medical Aides (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Garment Worker, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  v.20: no.3 (1978: Oct)
- Garment Worker, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  v.20: no.3 (1978: Oct); Copy #2
- Garment Worker, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  v.19: no.2 (1977: Nov)
- The Needlepoint, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  no. 17 (1954-Mar)
- The Needlepoint, 1957 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  no.39 (1957: Nov)
- The Needlepoint, 1960 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  no.55 (1960: June)
- The I.L.G.'er, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  v.16: no.3 (1965: Jan)
- Leslie Fay Workers' Newsletter, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  no.1 (1993: Nov.)
- Leslie Fay Workers' Newsletter, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  no.1 (1993: Nov.); Copy #2
- The Stitching Post, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  v.3: no.1 (1965: Jan-Feb)
- The Stitching Post, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  v.2: no.6 (1964: Nov-Dec)
- The Reporter, 1960 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  v.1: no.11 (1960: Sep)
- Unity News, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  v.1: no.1 (1972: Feb)
- Northeastern News (Box 72, Folder 11)
  v.25: no.8 (1960: Winter)
- Northeastern News, 1960 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  v.25: no.9 (1960: May)
- Northeastern News, 1960 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  (1960: August)
- Northeastern News, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  v.26: no.51 (1961: January)
- Northeastern News, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  v.26: no.52 (1961: March)
- Northeastern News, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  v.26: no.53 (1961: June-July)
- Northeastern News, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  v.26: no.54 (1961: September-October)
- Northeastern News, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  v.27: no. 55 (1961: December)
- Northeastern News, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  v.1: no. 3 (1984: September)
- Northeastern News, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  v.1: no. 3 (1984: September); Copy #2
- Northeastern News, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  v.1: no.3 (1984: September); Copy #3
- Northeastern News (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Northeastern News, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  v.1: no.1 (1959: December)
- Clem Lyons Retirement Dinner, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Desert Storm Musical Extravaganza, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Desert Storm Musical Extravaganza, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Convention, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  Day 6
- Family Planning Services Physical Examinations (Box 72, Folder 15)
- The Needle's Eye, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  n.109 (1976: March)
- The Needle's Eye, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  (1971: May); Only pages 3-6
- Everybody Sings (Box 72, Folder 17)
  Songbook
- Everybody Sings (Box 72, Folder 17)
  Soundbook; Copy #2
- Structure and Functioning if the ILGWU (Box 72, Folder 18)
- Structure and Functioning of the ILGWU (Box 72, Folder 18)
- ILG Raves of 1976. (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Pittson Guide (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.7: no. 1 (1980: March)
- Pittston Guide (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.7 no:1 (1980: March)
- Pittston Guide, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.6 no:1 (197: March)
- Pittston Guide, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.7: no.1 (1980: March); Copy #2
- Pittston Guide, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.6: no.2 (1979: October); Copy #2
- Pittston Guide, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.6: no.2 (1979: October)
- Pittston Guide, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.6: no.1 (1979: March)
- Pittston Guide, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.7: no.2 (1980: October)
- Pittston Guide, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Pittston Guide, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Pittston Guide, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Pittston Guide, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.5: no.3 (1978:Nov); Copy #2
- Pittston Guide, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.5: no3 (1978: Nov); Copy #3
- Pittston Guide, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.5: no.1 (1978: Jan)
- Pittston Guide, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.5: no.1 (1978: Jan); Copy #2
- Pittston Guide, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Pittston Guide, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.11: no.1 (1984: Oct)
- Pittston Guide, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.1: no.10 (1983: Spring)
- Pittston Guide, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Pittston Guide, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  v.10: no.1 (1983: Spring); Copy #3
- 35 Northeast, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 21)
- 35 Northeast, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 21)
- 35 Northeast, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 22)
- Northeast Department ILGWU Health and Welfare Fund, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 23)
- Northeast News, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 24)
- Songs of Work and Freedom (Box 72, Folder 25)
- 30th Anniversary, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 26)
- Contract with Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 27)
- ILGWU Delegate's Notebook (Box 72, Folder 28)
  Blank Copy
- ILGWU Delegate's Notebook (Box 72, Folder 28)
  Blank Copy #2
- ILGWU Delegate's Notebook (Box 72, Folder 28)
  Blank Copy #3
- Dressmakers' Joint Council and Northeast Apparel Association Contract, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 29)
- ILGWU History and Coloring Book (Box 72, Folder 30)
- Why Mondale?, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 31)
- Why Mondale?, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 31)
- Union Worker, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  v.1: no.1 (1977: Oct)
- Union Worker, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  (1978: Jan-Feb)
- Union Worker, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  (1979: March)
- Union Worker, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 32)
- Union Worker, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  (1979: Oct-Nov)
- Union Worker, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  (1980: March)
- Union Worker, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 32)
- Union Worker, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  (1980: Mar); Copy #2
- ILGWU Political Activity and the Law (Box 72, Folder 33)
- The Torch, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 34)
  v.10: no.1 (1977: Oct)
- Cindy Goes Shopping with Mommy (Box 72, Folder 35)
  Informative Buying Guide and Coloring Book
- Signature of 450,000 (Box 72, Folder 36)
- Solidarity, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 37)
- Convention Seating Map (Box 72, Folder 38)
- Interviews With Moe Diamond & Miscellaneous Pamphlets, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  [English, Chinese, Spanish]
- Local 10 Outerwear Bargainers Press Craft Terms on Eight Fronts, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  Newspaper Article; Cutters Column; May
- "Bohemia" (Box 75, Folder 3)
  Newspaper Article; Illustrated by Roberto Garcia; Spanish
- ILGWU Miscellaneous Articles & Copies, 1941 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Technological Changes in the Garment Industry [Volumes VIII, IX, X], 1984-1989 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  September 1984, February 1987, April 1989
- Ordinary People Extraordinary People, 2000 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  books, 2c; Debra E. Bernhardt & Rachel Bernstein
- Songs For Labor. Knitting Dictionary. Guide to the Manufacture of Sweaters, Knit Shirts and Swimwear, 1963- 1992 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  3 books/pamphlets
- Double Knit Fabric Manual. Tailor's Progress, 1944/1961 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  ILGWU Books
- The Women's Garment Workers: A History of the ILGWU, 1924 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  Book
- Miscellaneous ILGWU Pamphlets & Newsletters (Box 75, Folder 10)
  Chinese Included
- ILGWU Handbooks (Box 75, Folder 11)
- 25th Anniversary Local 91 ILGWU Illustrated Hardcover Book, 1913-1938 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  1913-1938
- ILGWU Health and Safety Manual, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 13)